

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary.

Lead cloud engineer at financial startup Dispute.com. Provided technical leadership and onboarded a team of 3 engineers, building a strong culture of documentation and testing. 8+ years of varied experience in software engineering specializing in backend development, software architecture, and real time applications. Strong communication skills, with a proven track record of leading teams to clarity on future and current products.

I love to learn new languages as well as deep learning every detail of more frequently used tools. Currently learning Rust, Bevy, and Vim. Specialist in C#, dotnet core, Unity, and Terraform. Excited by working with highly performant and reliable software with passionate teammates.

Work Experience

Dispute.com Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Remote)

SENIOR/LEAD SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Feb. 2023 - Present

- Designed and developed secure and scalable systems for a young startup using Azure (App Service, Sql Server, Functions, Application Insights, Entra Id, AAD).
- Introduced Auth0 for client authentication and authorization, automated management via Terraform.
- · Created extensible system to manage integrations with CRMs and Chargeback Protection platforms (Konnektive, Sticky, Ethoca, Verifi)
- Build foundational engineering practices to support a small team.
- · Created CI/CD pipelines in GitHub Actions which deployed applications via Terraform and released internal shared Nuget and NPM packages.

Flite Golf & Entertainment

Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Remote)

UNITY IMPLEMENTATION SPECIALIST

Seb. 2022 - Feb. 2023

- Provided company-wide guidance on C# and Unity best practices as the resident Unity expert.
- Reduced build times by splitting project code into assembly definitons.
- · Introduced unit tests to an untested codebase.
- Implemented extensible logging solution supporting both cloud-based analytics and local file logging.
- Introduced Azure Application Insights to capture logs and debug all deployments across all facilities.
- · Managed on-site deployment of 36 Unity-based golf simulators, and Flite's client relationship with the independent facility.
- Built foundation for disciplined QA practice by designing standarized test cases.
- · Led towards a culture of documentation and collaboration by creating a knowledge base and onboarding guide.

Centare (Milwaukee Tool)

Milwaukee, Wisconsin

AWS CLOUD ENGINEER

Jan. 2021 - Jun. 2021

- Used CQRS and Event Sourcing to build an ETL pipeline from Sql Server into Elasticsearch
- · Learned AWS Lambda and the Kinesis Consumer Library in Python to build a serverless data pipeline
- Skills: Python Terraform Docker C# AWS Lambda Dynamodb Kinesis

Centare (Symplr Cactus)

Milwaukee. Wisconsin Sep. 2019 - Dec. 2020

FULL STACK ANGULAR DEVELOPER

• Modernized existing web applications into Angular Single Page Applications.

- Onboarded two offshore teams to work inside the new project ecosystem.
- Skills: Angular Typescript RxJS Cypress C# Web API Agile

Centare (API Healthcare)

Milwaukee, Wisconsin

Aug. 2017 - Seb. 2019

CLOUD ENGINEER, ANGULAR APPLICATION DEVELOPER

- Converted legacy C# on-premise modules to run on the Azure cloud.
- Managed automated build and deployment in Jenkins.
- Worked on Time and Attendance software used by hospitals across US and Canada.
- Documented and led design decisions for Angular appliations.
- · Worked in an organization of 6+ other teams.
- · Onboarded new team members to support Angular applications by creating a knowledge base and one-on-one mentoring

Brady Corporation

Seoul, S.Korea

Jun. 2015 - Dec. 2016

IT DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Honors & Awards

INTERNATIONAL AWARDS

J.S.A
J.S.A
٠

DOMESTIC AWARDS

2021	2nd Place , AWS Korea GameDay	Seoul, S.Kored
2015	3rd Place , WITHCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Kored
2017	Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Kored
2013	Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Korea

COMMUNITY

- 2022 AWS Community Builder (Container), Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- 2022 HashiCorp Ambassador, HashiCorp
- 2018 **Organizer of HashiCorp Korea User Group**, HashiCorp

Certificates _____

2023	AWS Certified Advanced Networking - Specialty, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
2022	AWS Certified Security - Specialty, Amazon Web Services (AWS)

- 2022 **AWS Certified Solutions Architect Professional**, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- 2021 **AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate**, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- 2020 **Certified Kubernetes Application Developer (CKAD)**, The Linux Foundation
- 2023 HashiCorp Certified: Consul Associate (002), HashiCorp
- 2023 HashiCorp Certified: Terraform Associate (003), HashiCorp

Education _____

MSOE Milwaukee, Wi

B.S. IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERINGSome stuff happened.

n Software Engineering Sept. 2012 - May 2017